http://www.fibreformelectronics.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICY- Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make use of the online product catalog at this site. This policy may change from time to time so please re-visit this page periodically. Web sites, which are linked to this site, may have different policies and Fibreform is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.
DISCLOSURE AND USE OF INFORMATION – Any personal information you provide on this site may be used, held or shared by Fibreform and its affiliates, associated companies, agents, distributors or others to fulfill your technical requirements and provide you services associated with our products.
Fibreform does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others outside of the Fibreform organization. We may disclose information in special cases when we believe in good faith that such release is necessary to comply with law, to identify or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our conditions of use and terms of service, to enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements, or protect the rights, property or safety of Fibreform or others. Any information you give us through this site may be transmitted to servers outside the country where the information was entered, and may be used, stored and processed outside of the country where it was entered.
We may use certain information gathered from this site to compile demographic data about our users, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information. If provided to third parties, this data will include no personally identifying information.
SECURITY – We will use every reasonable effort to ensure the security of our system and will strive to protect any personal information you provide through this site. Unfortunately, we cannot guarantee that all data transmitted over the Internet will be secure.
CNC Turning, Milling, Machining
Fabrication
Casting & Hogouts
Temperature Controlled jig boring, +/- .0001
Quote
View Product Gallery
More
(714) 898-9641
Latest News:
Fibreform Precision Machining Announces a Joint Venture with Delta Machine  >
[Read More]
A Message to Our Customers, Colleagues and Friends  >
[Read More]
Fibreform Successfully Delivers the First Parts for Northrop Grumman‘s Joint Strike Fighter Program  >
[Read More]
Latest News:
Fibreform Precision Machining Announces a Joint Venture with Delta Machine  >
[Read More]
A Message to Our Customers, Colleagues and Friends  >
[Read More]
Fibreform Successfully Delivers the First Parts for Northrop Grumman‘s Joint Strike Fighter Program  >
[Read More]
Customer Approvals Include: Raytheon, Northrop Grumman, Lockheed Martin, & More
